tennisexpress.com 2014-06-21

# Tennis Express Customer Privacy Policy | Tennis Express - Tennis Express

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy and security of our visitors is extremely important to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information received and collected by Tennis Express and how it is used.

**How Secure is my Purchase Information?**

Tennis Express is VeriSign Trusted for secure e-commerce transactions and communications. This partnership prevents any information from being accessed by unauthorized sources.

**Does Tennis Express Share Information?**

Tennis Express does not share or sell personal information or e-mail addresses gathered from customers with other businesses or websites.

**What Does Tennis Express Collect?**

Like many other Web sites, Tennis Express makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**What about Cookies on Tennis Express?**

Tennis Express uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, to record user-specific information such as which pages the user accesses or visits, and to customize Web page content based on browser type and other information that the visitor sends via their browser. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser settings. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Who Else Is Advertising On Tennis Express?**

We employ the use of third-party ad servers or ad networks. Third-parties use cookies and may have access to personal information needed to perform functions (such as saving your preferences in order to advertise specifically on your IP address) and so that they may collect demographic data. Tennis Express' privacy policy does not apply to such outside advertisers or web sites. Consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about disabling services.

**Managing Email Subscription**

To Unsubscribe from Tennis Express emails, click the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email message. When you reach the Web page, ensure that all check boxes are unselected and click the submit button.

For more information or questions concerning our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **cs@tennisexpress.com** or call us at ** ** **713-435-4818**.
